rhinospike.com 2015-12-28

# RhinoSpike : Privacy Policy

last updated February 4th, 2010 

## 1\. INTRODUCTION AND POLICY UPDATES

This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") covers our treatment of personally identifiable information Azabua, LLC ("Azabua," "we," "our" or "us") collect online when you access the Rhinospike World Wide Web Site located at http://www.rhinospike.com and the content and services provided therein (collectively, the "Site" or "Rhinospike"). This Privacy Policy applies and is limited to the treatment of information that is collected via the Site.

Azabua takes the privacy of your personally identifiable information seriously and will strive to use your personally identifiable information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Please review this Privacy Policy carefully.

## 2\. INFORMATION GATHERING

### PERSONAL INFORMATION

When you sign up for Rhinospike, you provide your email address. After registration we give you the opportunity to provide additional profile information, such as your name, location and native language. In some cases we may ask for additional information for security reasons or to provide specific services to you. **Once you register you can visit your profile at any time to add or remove personal information about yourself**. You may visit your Account settings page to change your email address.

### CONTENT

The primary function of Rhinospike is for users to share content. This includes uploading audio files and submitting text. If you do not want us to store metadata associated with content you share on Rhinospike (such as audio files), please remove the metadata before uploading the content.

### SITE ACTIVITY INFORMATION

We keep track of the actions you take on Rhinospike, such as adding a friend, submitting an Audio Request or uploading an audio file. In some cases you are also taking an action when you provide information or content to us. For example, if you share an audio file, in addition to storing the actual content you uploaded, we might log the fact you shared it. 

### ACCESS DEVICE AND BROWSER INFORMATION

When you access Rhinospike from a computer, mobile phone, or other device, we may collect information from that device about your browser type, location, and IP address, as well as the pages you visit.

### COOKIES

Certain pages of the Site may use persistent and/or sessional cookies (i.e. small data files that our web servers may send to your computer when you visit the Site) to track your usage of the Site. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You have the option to reject the Site's cookies and still use the Site, but you may not be able to access or use some of the features on the Site.

## 3\. INFORMATION USAGE

Rhinospike uses collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research.

In addition, we may share with others (including without limitation our advertisers, marketers, and vendors) aggregated and/or anonymous information that we have collected based on usage of the Site or statistical information that we have compiled about our users.

We transfer information about you if Azabua or Rhinospike is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, we will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

## 4\. OTHER

### LINKS

Our Site may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We recommend that you review the privacy policies of those sites when you visit them.

### CHANGES

Azabua may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by posting a notice on the Site. Please check the Site from time to time for the most current version of our Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Site after we have notified you of such changes as described above constitutes your acceptance of such changes.

### QUESTIONS

Any questions about this privacy policy should be addressed to support at rhinospike dot com.
